Justin Edwards

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

Clearwater, FL 727-389-4076 justin@jedwards.cc

Links

Website

<u>GitHub</u>

LinkedIn

Skills

JavaScript/TypeScript

Python

Go

SQL/Redis

React/NextJs

AWS

OpenAI/LLMs

Projects

Atlantis Health

Patient Portal

Dashboard for managing treatment

Adele

Al Powered Medication Assistant

Personal

ChatUI

Manage OpenAI chats and agents

<u>SearchAl</u>

Al Assisted Search

go-kerbal

CLI mod manager for KSP

nn-cars

Train car to drive in 2D game

Contributions

tailwindlabs/tailwindcss.com

hhursev/recipe-scrapers

About

Full-Stack Developer specializing in TypeScript, NextJs, PostgreSQL, and AWS. Experienced in delivering diverse projects from AI assistants to user portals for the pharmaceutical industry. Capable of leading projects from design to production, managing codebases, and coordinating small developer teams. Advocate for agile methodologies and code reviews, committed to innovation and continuous improvement in software development.

Employment History

Full-Stack Developer, Atlantis Health, Remote

AUGUST 2022 - PRESENT

- Delivered full-stack applications for healthcare giants like Sanofi, Jazz
 Pharmaceuticals, and Novartis, utilizing agile methodologies and scrum for efficient team collaboration and task management.
- Spearheaded the development of a 25-page NextJs website, including a
 dashboard, account management, and static content, demonstrating proficiency in
 handling large-scale projects.
- Integrated IBM Watson's NLP capabilities into a patient treatment support application, leveraging RESTFul APIs, NextJs, and Tailwind CSS, leading to extended user engagement.
- Boosted legacy app's performance by 80% and introduced user authentication, personalization, reminders, and SMS features using Python, NextJs, Tailwind CSS, GraphQL, and MySQL.
- Accelerated CI/CD deploy times on AWS infrastructure by 200% and optimized development workflow through code-reviews and Python and Node.js automation scripts.
- Promoted effective teamwork with cross-functional teams using Asana, planning, and retrospective meetings, resulting in ahead-of-schedule project completion with minimal issues.

Product Support Specialist, VantagePoint AI, Remote

JANUARY 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

- Maintained extensive knowledge of software platform that used AI to predict stock market changes
- Identified and reported bugs to development team, enhancing product stability and user experience
- Resolved Salesforce support tickets with exceptional customer service, providing timely and accurate records
- Coordinated with Software Potential to manage customer information and licensing
- Supported users in troubleshooting software issues, creating helpful knowledge base articles, improving user satisfaction and engagement

Live Entertainment Technician, Freelance

MARCH 2015 - MAY 2022

- Led and trained crews for diverse events and resolved technical issues swiftly
- Steered problem-solving initiatives during productions, ensuring smooth events
- Participated in various aspects of production, including set design, painting, and electrics

Education

BAS in Technology Development and Management, St. Petersburg College, Clearwater, FL

MAY 2022

Acquired skills in technology development, project management, and IT service delivery. This comprehensive program allowed for adaptation to the rapidly evolving technology landscape and prepared for leadership roles in the field.